fairchildsemi.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy

### Energy Efficient Innovations  
  
---  
Rate this webpage  
  
## Need  
Support?

##  Home >  Privacy Policy

Effective Date: August 30, 2018.

Welcome! Thank you for visiting Semiconductor Components Industries, LLC (“ON Semiconductor,” “we” or “our”). To help inform you, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of information you submit or we collect through our website www.onsemi.com and our other related mobile websites, services, tools, mobile applications and other applications to which this Privacy Policy is linked (the “Site”). The Site is owned and operated by ON Semiconductor.

## Contents & Summary

A table summarizing the contents of this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") appears below, followed by the policy in full. Should there be any discrepancy between the table and the full Privacy Policy, the language of the full Privacy Policy shall govern.

## Scope and Consent

By using the Site you expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information and other information as described in this Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site is also governed by the Terms of Use.

## Information Collection

We collect the following information when you use the Site.

**(a) Registration and Account Information:** When you create an account or profile on the Site, you voluntarily give us personal information, including sensitive information, which may include your name, username, address, phone number, email address, payment information, resume etc.

**(b) Information to Respond to Your Requests:** You may also give us your personal information to sign up for our newsletters and other communications.

**(c) Information From Other Sources:** We may, on occasion, combine information from outside sources to customize your experience on the Site.

**(d) Mobile Information:** If you access our Site through a mobile device (e.g. your unique device identifier, your device’s operating system, your network connection or the mobile carrier for your phone).

**(e) Technical usage information:** We use tracking technologies such as cookies to measure usage. For more information about the use of cookies and similar technologies on our online services please review our Tracking Technologies Policy. 

## Uses and Retention

We use information collected from you to operate our Site and contact you. Your information is retained for as long as we need it for our business.. 

## Your Choices

You can control how and when you want to receive notifications from ON Semiconductor on the Site or by following instructions within the notices. 

## Disclosure of Information

We may share your personal information and other information we collect with the following entities: (1) ON Semiconductor and the rest of  our corporate family; (2) our service providers and contractors; (3) other entities with your consent; (4) legal and law enforcement; (5) others if there is a change of control; (6) ad networks; (7) social networks; (9) data analytics companies.

## Tracking Technologies (Cookies)

We use tracking technologies (including cookies) to recognize you, customize your experience on the Site, and target the content/advertising you see, including providing videos customized to your interests. You consent to our tracking of your video viewing through the Site or third party social media.

## Access and Review Options

You can review and edit your personal information by accessing your account on the Site.

## California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you may request information about our practices related to disclosing your personal information. 

## EU and Swiss Data Subject Rights

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) or Switzerland, you have the right to: (a) request access to your personal data; (b) request erasure of your personal data; (c) request restrictions on the processing your personal data; (d) object to processing your personal data; and/or (e) the right to data portability. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

## Third Parties

We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites that are linked to our Site. 

## Security

We protect your personal information using security measures.

## Children’s Privacy

The Site is not intended for children under the age of 13.

## International Transfer

We store and process your personal information on our computers in the US and elsewhere in the world.

## Global Privacy Standards

ON Semiconductor is governed by applicable global privacy standards.

## Notification Regarding Updates

You agree that we may notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting notices on this Site.

## Contact Us

ON Semiconductor privacy issues are covered by the Global Privacy Office. For more information about our privacy practices, go to our full  Privacy Policy or send an email to [privacy@onsemi.com. ](mailto:privacy@onsemi.com)

## 1\. Scope and Consent.

When you use the Site, you are contracting with ON Semiconductor located at 5005 East McDowell Road, Phoenix, AZ 85008. If you reside outside of the United States, ON Semiconductor is your data controller. By using the Site, you expressly consent to our collection, use, disclosure, and retention of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

## 2\. Information We Collect.

**(a) Registration and Account Information:** You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information (i.e., name, email address, phone number, mobile telephone number and physical contact information) about yourself. If you choose to register for an account with us, we require you to create a username and password, you choose to give us your personal information and are not anonymous to us. When you register an account, create a profile, purchase products, or otherwise engage with our Site, you may provide personal information such as name, physical address, email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, payment information, zip codes, and other relevant information. Personal information is only associated with your account/profile when you sign in as a registered user. We also collect information relating to the business you represent and demographic information such as domain information, zip codes and areas of interest. 

**(b) Information to respond to your requests:** You may give us your personal information so we can respond to your requests, send you newsletters and other communications you request. Details of how you can opt-out of receiving any communications from us are detailed in the section headed “Your Choices” below.

**(c) Information From Other Sources:** The information we collect may be combined with information from outside records that we have acquired in accordance with the law and/or your permission. For example, we may, on occasion, combine information from outside sources to process your application for a position or otherwise as per section 2(f) below. 

**(d) Mobile Information:** If you access the Site through a mobile device we may collect additional information from you (e.g. your unique device identifier or a mobile number).

**(e) Technical Usage Information:** When you visit our Site, we collect usage information sent to us by your computer, mobile, or other access device that tells us how you are using the Sites (“usage information”). We use tracking technologies (including pixel tags, cookies, flash cookies, web beacons, clear GIFs, embedded scripts, Javascript, local storage and e-tags/cache browsers) to collect usage information. 

We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and/or connection information. During some visits we may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages and page interaction information. 

Our goal is to collect and use only that information that we think is required for our legitimate business interests (e.g., for contract or employee hiring purposes), in order to better understand your interests and improve your experience of using the Site. To learn more about how we use tracking technologies and cookies, see  Section 8 of this Privacy Policy  and click here for our full Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy.

The provision of personal data is either a requirement necessary to obtain the services that you might request and/or for us to operate our business, including our Site. You are required to provide the data set forth above if you want to receive the products and/or services outlined in this section. Failure to provide the data will prevent us from being able to provide services you request or otherwise inhibit our ability to operate the Site.

**(f) Employee and Prospective Employee Information:** When you register an account to learn about career opportunities with ON Semiconductor, submit an application, resume or C.V. for employment or otherwise engage with our Site, you may provide personal information. Where you submit information on behalf of another person, you confirm that you have made that person aware of how we may collect, use and disclose their information, the reason you have provided it, how they can contact us, the terms of this Privacy Policy and that they have consented to such collection, use and disclosure.

## 3\. Uses and Retention.

**(a) Operate Our Site:** We use the information collected to (i) respond to your requests or orders; (ii) provide customer service (e.g., to resolve disputes, feedback, problems with your account/profile or the Site); (iii) receive and process your applications or resumes for jobs with us (iii) personalize your experience by providing content on the Site, including targeted advertising/communications, that we believe may be of most interest to you; (iv) improve the Site; (v) give you information about your account; and (v) provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience.

**(b) Analyze and Aggregate Non-Personal Information:** We use aggregate information about our users and non-personal information to analyze Site and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports.

**(c) Prevent Fraud:** We use information from the Site to prevent, detect, and investigate fraud, security breaches, and potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms of Use.

**(d) Communicate With You:** We use your information to contact you to maintain the Site, your account, or to comply with your stated communication preferences, or to provide other services requested by you, as described at the time when we collect the information from you, or to contact you for other purposes authorized by law.

**(e) Employee, Prospective Employee and Contractor Information:** Your personal information will be stored in our systems for our business and administration purposes to consider you for employment or contracting, and may be used by ON Semiconductor as necessary for these purposes. We collect employment –related personal information for career purposes including to:

  * select suitable staff 
  * facilitate the administration of staff and their records 
  * contact next-of-kin 
  * manage staff throughout the term of their engagement, including to ensure that competent, trained staff are utilized and to assist in performance management and career development 
  * maintain archival material in respect of former staff 
  * conduct internal research
  * conduct investigations of suspicious or harmful activity
  * conduct marketing and data analysis 
  * send you updates and news concerning ON Semiconductor and its business partners 
  * assist you with any future requirements, including to answer reasonable inquiries by any of your future employers and 
  * comply with ON Semiconductor’s legal obligations

**(f) Marketing Analysis:** We may use the information (including personal data) for marketing analysis. 

**(g) Data Retention:** Your information will be retained in accordance with our data retention policy which is designed to retain data for as long as needed for us to comply with our contractual obligations, employment obligations, and other business purposes, including global legal obligations to retain data.

## 4\. Your Choices.

You can control how and when you want to receive notifications from ON Semiconductor on the Site or by following instructions within the notices. If you have consented to our collection of your personal data for multiple specific purposes or explicitly consented to our collection of special/sensitive categories of personal data (i.e., personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, and the processing of genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or data concerning a natural person's sex life or sexual orientation) your consent can be withdrawn at an any time without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. For more information about how to opt-out of marketing communications go to  Section 7 (Communication Preferences and Marketing (Opt-out)), and for information about how to change, update your personal information go to Section 9 (Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Personal Information). For more information about the rights of European Economic Area (EEA) or Swiss residents go to Section 11 (EU and Swiss Data Subject Rights). 

## 5\. Disclosure.

Information collected on the Site may be shared with: 

**(a) The ON Semiconductor Corporate Family.** We may share the information we collect about you with the ON Semiconductor corporate family and their and our affiliates and subsidiaries, as well as with third party suppliers and service providers. The information may be disclosed (i) to provide joint content and our services (e.g., registration, transactions, analytics and customer support); (ii) to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts, violations of our policies, fraud and/or data security breaches; (iii) to guide decisions about our, ON Semiconductor or third party’s business, assets, operations, rights, products, sites, applications, services, tools, and communications and (iv) processing and storage of information. Members of our corporate family will use this information to send you marketing communications and you will have the opportunity to opt-out in email communications.

**(b) Service Providers and Other Third Parties.** We may disclose your information to service providers under contract who help with our business operations (such as, but not limited to, fraud investigations, bill collection, payment processing, shipment; recruitment, employment, research, and site analytics and operations). We may also share your information with third parties to defend against legal claims; to investigate, prevent, or act against illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to safety, or violations of ON Semiconductor’s terms of use; to protect our operations, assets, and intellectual property; to allow us to pursue appropriate legal remedies or limit damages; to pursue any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer of assets, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock; or as otherwise required by law.

**(c) Other Entities with your Consent.** Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).

**(d) Legal and Law Enforcement.** Law enforcement, governmental agencies, or authorized third parties, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other ON Semiconductor user to legal liability. In such events, we will only disclose information relevant and necessary to the investigation or inquiry, such as name, city, state, ZIP code, telephone number, email address, user ID history, IP address, fraud complaints, and anything else we may deem relevant to the investigation.

**(e) Change of Control – New Owners.** Other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will make reasonable efforts to request that the new combined entity follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information would be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.

**(f) Ad Networks.** On the Site, we may work with third parties to serve advertisement, provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement and site analytics and assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit or set their own tracking technologies/cookies. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. They might also obtain information about other applications that you have downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit and other information about you or your device in order to analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Site and elsewhere. For more information about third party ad servers at our Site and your ability to opt-out of targeted advertising from such third parties, please visit [ Ad Choices](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/).

**(g) Companies In The Mobile Industry.** If you access the Site through a mobile device, we may also share your information with Carriers, operating systems and platforms.

## 6\. Information You Share on the Site. 

If you post information or content, such as by posting photos, commenting on a blog, or participating in online forums or communities, or when you interact with our Site through social media sites, plug-ins or other applications, depending upon your privacy settings, this information may become public on the Internet. We cannot prevent further use of this information. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. Please refer to those third party sites’ privacy policies and terms of use to learn more about their privacy practices, which we do not control.

## 7\. Communication Preferences and Marketing (Opt-out).

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize the Site. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us, you can indicate your communications preference within the direct communication from us or through your account/profile settings. You may not opt-out of administrative emails (for example, emails about your transactions or policy changes) for your registered account.

## 8\. Tracking Technologies (Cookies).

When you visit the Site, we and our business partners may use tracking technologies to enhance your online experience or customize our offerings.

A few additional important things you should know about our use of tracking technologies (cookies):

  * We offer certain features that are available only through the use of tracking technologies.
  * We use both session and persistent tracking technologies. Tracking technologies (e.g., cookies) can either be persistent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). You are always free to decline tracking technologies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Site. Refer to the help section of your browser, browser extensions, or installed applications for instructions on blocking, deleting, or disabling tracking technologies such as cookies.
  * If you are a registered user and you specifically request that our Site remembers your login information, you are allowing us to place a permanent cookie onto your computer. 
  * You may encounter tracking technologies/cookies from our third party service providers, that we have allowed on our site that assist us with various aspects of our web site operations and services, such as  Google Analytics 
  * You also may encounter tracking technologies from third parties on certain pages of the websites that we do not control and have not authorized. (For example, if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a cookie placed by that web page).
  * We may target and track the videos you view on the Site. You consent to our tracking of your video viewing through the Site or third party social media for up to two years or as permitted by applicable law.

For more information about the use of cookies and similar technology on our online services please review this Privacy Policy and our Cookies and Tracking Technologies Policy. 

## 9\. Accessing, Reviewing, and Changing Your Personal Information.

Registered members can review and change personal information at any time by accessing their accounts on the Site. You should promptly update your personal information if it changes or becomes inaccurate. We may retain some information from closed accounts so that we can comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, enforce our Terms of Use, or take other actions permitted by law. Likewise if your account or membership is terminated or suspended, we may maintain some information to prevent re-registration.

## 10\. Notice to California Residents.

**How Do We Respond to Do Not Track Signals for California Residents.** California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b)(as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how ON Semiconductor responds to “Do Not Track” browser settings. ON Semiconductor does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created. 

## 11\. EU and Swiss Data Subject Rights.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) or Switzerland, you have the right to: (a) request access to your personal data and rectification of inaccurate personal data; (b) erasure of your personal data; (c) request restrictions on the processing of your personal data; (d) object to processing your personal data; and/or (e) the right to data portability. 

For information about how to get access to personal data and for exercising your rights, please refer to the Contact section of this privacy policy.

You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

## 12\. Third Parties.

Our Site may contain links to other third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these third party sites.

## 13\. Security.

We store and process your information on our servers located in the United States and around the world. We maintain technical, physical, and administrative security measures to protect the security of your personal information against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or alteration. It is your responsibility to make sure that your personal information is accurate. If you believe that your login credentials have been compromised, please make sure to contact us as indicated in the  Contact Us Section, below .

## 14\. Children's Privacy.

The Site is a general audience site and it is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information via our websites, applications, services, or tools from users in this age group. ON Semiconductor requires that you be 18 years of age to work in any of our facilities.

## 15\. International Transfer.

As we operate internationally, and many of our computer systems are currently based in the U.S. your personal information may be processed in the U.S. and elsewhere where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create an account/profile, you consent to the collection and/or processing in the U.S. of your personal information and tracking technologies/cookies as described in this Policy. You understand that the U.S. government may obtain access to the personal data you submit if necessary for investigative purposes (e.g., terrorism investigation). We use adequate means to transfer data under applicable laws (e.g., EU Standard Contractual Clauses, model contracts/transfer agreements, privacy principles, privacy statements, privacy policies, and other country-specific registrations and filings).

## 16\. Global Privacy Standards.

ON Semiconductor’s operation of the Site is in accordance with global standards and consistent with EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles. With respect to the processing of personal data received or transferred pursuant to the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, ON Semiconductor is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission.

Consistent with EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles, ON Semiconductor commits to resolve complaints on its processing of personal information. EU/EEA and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact the Global Privacy Office at [privacy@onsemi.com](mailto:privacy@onsemi.com). 

ON Semiconductor is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives under the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf.

If ON Semiconductor does not resolve your complaint, you may submit your complaint free of charge to <https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-claim>, ON Semiconductor’s designated independent dispute resolution provider. Under certain conditions specified by the principles of the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, you may also be able to invoke binding arbitration to resolve your complaint. Additional information on this option is available in [Annex I of the Privacy Shield Principles](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction).

ON Semiconductor complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States. ON Semiconductor has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles for the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks. The following U.S. subsidiaries of our organization are also adhering to the Privacy Shield Principles for the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Frameworks and are covered by our Privacy Shield self-certifications: (a) Aptina, LLC, (b) Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation, and (c) Semiconductor Components Industries, LLC. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. For more information about the ON Semiconductor global privacy practices and principles, please contact the Global Privacy Office with any 

## 17\. Notification Regarding Updates.

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat personal information by placing a notice on the Site. You should check the Site frequently for updates. We will also notify you of any material changes in the way that we collect or use your personal data.
